<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<title>BINNENGEKOMEN.</title>
	<p>ZOLTKAMP, 28 Nov. Wybren Bomer, do Jong, Newc. HARLINGEN, 28 Nov. Sud Kampen, Woudstra, Warkworth - Svanen, Hakker, Riga. - Osmu, Efelund, Oostace. - Birling.s. Newcastle.</p>
	<p>DELFZIJL, 29 Nov. Amicitia, Sprik, Riga. - Jacoba, Engelhard, Frederikstad. - Bertha, Boomgaarden, Gnetzrjl. - Jonge Herman, Weken,</p>
	<p>HELLEVOETSLÜIS,29Nov. W.Z.W. Claverhouse, Parsons, Banana. - Mathilde, Schulte, Riaoer. - Francesschina, Mortola, Brouwersh. - üronning Louise, Larsen, id. - Krimpen a/d. Lek, V. d. Stoop, ïierikzee. MAASSLUIS, 29 Nov. W. Lord Eaglan, S., Newc. - Kinghorn, Alida, S, Middlesbro&apos;. - Shotton, S., Kroonstad. - Seeunda, S., Liban. — Ter reede: Familiens Haab, Belsen, Libau - Adler, Heideman, Sundsvall.</p>
	<p>— De stoomboot Talisman is met defecte machine uit zee teruggekomen. DORDRECHT, 28 Nov. Greve Trys, Petersen, Livorno. BROUWERSHAVEN, 29 Nov. W.Z.W. Elisabeth Maria, Opstelten, Tjilatjap n. Rott; vertr. 4 Aug. - Olive, Eyre, Londen. - John Panton, Gook, Newc. EMÜEN, 24 Nov. Onrast, Aukes, Groningen. - Antje, Stiermann, Holland. - Franciska, Bleeker, id.</p>
	<p>MALMÖ, 29 Nov. Vidar, S., Amst. NORRKOPING, vóór 24 Nov. Alliancc, de Jonge, Dronth. BEVAL, 23 Nov. Hermanus Wigher, Waslander, Biirdeaux l.v. Dautzig.</p>
	<p>GRIMSBY, 28 Nov. Cornelia, Teensma, Stookh. n. Rochtster. CARDIFF, 27 Nov. Harmonie, Doewes, Landerman. — 28 Nov. Gottfried, Reicb, Amst. j B ELF AST, 28 Nov. Quail, S, Estt. W. HARTL^POOL,27 Nov. Conatio. S„ Schiedam. i GRIMdBY, 27 Nov. Southella, S., Rott. i GOOLE, 27 Nov. R. Maion, S, Rott. BHIKLDS, 27 Nov. Chiswick, S., Schiedam. j GRaNGEMOUTH, 27 Nov. Glasgow, S., Rott. - Uaie, Parrei \ Gothenburg. I A BERÜJEEN, 26 Nov. Bon Accord, S, Rott. &apos; ■ STOCKTON, 27 Nov. 3 Gebroeders, Douwes, Halmstad. SUNDERLAND, 27 Nov. Juno, Dedinafleld, Rott. Bij LIZARD, 28 Nor. Albatros, Lnpkus, Rio Grande, n. Faim. FALKOUTH, 28 Nov. Julius, Blanke, Kio Grande. Bij DUNGENESS, 27 Nev. Abraham, Visser, Amst. n. Padarg. BALTIMORE, 23 Nov. Antoinette, Kosenou, Bremen. Bij St.-HELENA, 22 Oct. Professor Simon, Thomas, Pot, Bat. n. Rott. — 30 Oct. Wijk aan Zee, de Looper, &apos;i jilatjap, n. Amst — ! 3 Nor. Lieutenant, Cowper, Padang n. New-Y&quot; ork.&apos; — 5 Nov. An: toinctte, de Boer qq., Bat. n Acast. St. HELENA, 7 Oct. Mndoleine.Pateau Culcutlan. Jamaica, i 8 Oct. W.J.Lewis.Trefry, Manilla n. New-York. — :OOet Ells; we-rth, Smith, Soerabaja n. Falm — 13 Oct CLveland, üevan, , Cheribon n. id. - Charlotte A. Littlefield, Carver, CalcuttaH. \ F».lui.-Mystery, Gibo.Swatown Londen. — 15 Oct. California, Deinum, Tjilatjap; v«rtr. 17 n Amst. — 17Oct John Milton, : Murphy, Ho Ho n.Cork. - AnnetLyle, Yeo, Rombay n. Liverp - : Reigatê, Robertson, Coconada n. Lenden.—23 Oct. Crcsswcll, j White, Ha Ho n. Falm. - Calano, Gedye-, Penang n. Lond. - Stieva Bloosa, Scett, Bombay n. Huil. - Wandering Chief, Brown, Saaa! rang n. Fair».- 30 Oct. Stockbridge, Laing, Calcutta n. Londen. - ; Noach 11, v. Schelven, Bat; vertr. n. Rott-Jarawar, Brandt, j Calcutta n. Trinidad - British Crown, Aadrew, Hongkong 5. Lonj den. - Africao, Larmer, Plym. n. Kaap de Goede Hoop. — 31 Oct. I St Lawror.ee, Johnsen, Madras n. Londen. — 1 Nov. Caroline, j I&apos;urnfcull. Cebu n. id. - Cbateau Lafit&apos;e, Decomhe, Manilla n. id - John H. Kimball, Humphreys, Yokohaman. Falm. - Accrington, I bimpson, Calcutta n. Dund*e. - Holliadside, Sim, Gjpalpeorn. ; Londen. — 2 Hef. Onward, Stimso», Hongkong n. id. - Wleo j Browsn, Beeehmg, Kobe n. id. - Belle Alliance. Hovrat, Msuritius iSa C°rk&apos; T 4 Not Augustme Kobbe, Carver, Adelaide n. Falm. - Aubrey Pake, Paisons, Samarang n. id.</p>
</text>
